(All characters and organisations in this drama are fictional.)
(Filming with minors followed broadcast guidelines,)
(and generative AI was used in select scenes.)
(Danger: Fall Hazard)
(Samcheon Cement)
Watch out.
(Episode 4)
You bastard.
Do you have any idea what that money was for?
Darn it.
Sir.
Without that money, my family of six...
Will be out on the street.
Please, the money you scammed from me...
Please give it back, sir.
Scam? Who scammed who, you punk?
Hey.
Scam?
Help me.
Kim Mu Jin, wake up.
Kim Mu Jin.
Kim Mu Jin, please wake up.
(Paramedics)
Where did he get hurt?
How?
How badly is he hurt?
(Chairman Hong OK Seon)
What on earth happened?
It's not life-threatening, is it?
Right?
(Yeoltan Pork Belly)
(Dad)
- Dad, I'll call you back in a... - Gyu Rim.
Dad.
By any chance, do you have some money?
(Surgery In Progress)
(Operating Room)
Hello.
Yoon Jin.
What happened? What happened to your face, Dad?
We lost our house.
What do you mean?
We're about to be thrown out on the street.
What are you talking about?
Well...
What are these?
Overdue notices, collection letters,
A foreclosure and an eviction notice.
You never came home, but you sure managed to hide these.
I knew you'd all freak out if you knew,
So I had someone else take care of them.
You took out a loan against this house?
Well, I was going to pay it all back,
But some bastards scammed me.
I lost sleep trying to get that money back.
I even did a stakeout.
I'm lucky to be alive.
Turns out those bastards were gangsters.
They're really nasty,
And absolutely terrifying.
By any chance,
Do you guys have any money?
Just enough for a security deposit on a monthly rental.
For the six of us to move out right away,
We need at least two rooms, for the men and women,
And one bathroom.
Let's just all fend for ourselves.
It's not like we've ever been that close anyway.
Dad can go his way, Han Gyu Rim can go hers,
And I'll go mine.
Gyu Oh is old enough to be on his own.
So let's all split up and take care of ourselves.
Then what about Gyu Min and Gyu Seo? What about the twins?
Since when have you cared so much about them?
After their mom ran off when they were three,
You left them with Han Gyu Rim and washed your hands of them.
Stop it.
Why? Am I lying?
You need to snap out of it too.
Raising them for ten years is more than enough.
I'm telling you, just drop them off at an orphanage already.
Will you shut your mouth, Han Gyu Young?
Leave the kids out of this,
And if you want to leave, then you leave.
Fine, I'll be the one to leave. I'm leaving this miserable house.
That girl has such a temper.
I wonder who she takes after.
But you're just like me, Gyu Rim.
When do we have to be out of this house?
Soon.
Immediately.
Well...
Do you really not have any money?
You really don't have anything stashed away?
- I'll pay you back with interest. - I'll see what I can do.
Wait.
Gyu Rim.
You truly are the eldest daughter of this family.
You know...
You're my lifeline, right?
Gosh, seriously...
I'm leaving.
You all have a nice, happy life together.
(Jung Woo)
Hello?
- Gyu Rim. - Jung Woo.
The surgery went well, and they moved him...
To his room a little while ago.
Why was Mu Jin at a construction site?
Oh, well...
He was worried about you, so he told me not to say anything.
Mu Jin...
Got kicked out of his house,
So he was working a part-time job at a construction site.
You must be Han Gyu Rim.
I'm Mu Jin's older sister.
You didn't know...
He was working at a construction site?
He's never lifted a single brick in his life.
He must have reeked of pain relief patches,
And you didn't notice a thing?
- Should we sit here? - Sure.
What's that pain patch smell?
What?
I hurt myself a little working out at the gym earlier.
You should be more careful. Let me see.
See what?
- Come on, let me see. - No, I'm fine.
- Is it bad? - No, I'm okay.
And you didn't know he left home...
And was living in a tiny studio, did you?
What do you even know about Mu Jin?
He gave up everything for you.
Let Mu Jin go.
He is not someone...
You can handle.
Please.
Han Gyu Rim.
Sweetie.
Stop crying.
They said the surgery was a success, okay?
It's my fault.
I hated him so much...
I wished he'd just break his leg. That's why...
Oh, sweetie, it's not your fault.
I'm telling you, it's not because of you.
He'll wake up soon, right?
He's going to be okay, right?
Of course.
Oh dear, you're going to collapse at this rate.
Aren't you dizzy? Do you want some water?
Oh my gosh. You must be so shocked.
You must live in this neighbourhood.
No.
I mean, yes.
People are going to think we're a real couple.
It seems so.
Right now,
I'm confessing to you.
Asking you to look at me, and only me.
I'm saying I think I like you, Gyu Rim.
If I don't confess my feelings to you right now,
I really feel like I'll lose you,
And my heart is pounding like crazy.
I really had to work up the courage for this.
You just keep letting your heart flutter for me.
You don't have to show it.
But it'd be even better if you did.
Whether it's a mess or not,
I'll go anywhere as long as I'm with you, Gyu Rim.
So don't you run away either.
Gyu Rim, could I...
Hug you?
Break up? Why would we break up?
That will never happen as long as you don't leave me.
I was worried all day that you were going to break up with me.
Do you know how scared I was?
(Seized Item)
You can't take that off.
What is this?
They put that there to show it's not ours anymore.
There are stickers on my bed and desk too.
Gyu Seo, I'll buy you a new bed and desk soon.
(Seized Item)
Hello, this is Han Gyu Rim.
Just give me 100,000 dollars.
100,000 dollars?
100,000 dollars for leaving Mu Jin.
That sounds like a pretty good deal, don't you think?
A deal?
To be honest,
When I heard Mu Jin was from a rich family,
I was surprised, but a part of me was thrilled.
I thought, "Am I going to be a Cinderella,"
"just like in the movies?"
"I won't have to struggle through this miserable life anymore."
I was so happy. Truly.
But then he was kicked out of his house...
And got hurt working at a construction site.
This isn't right.
This isn't how things should be.
The more I thought about it, the more unsettling it was.
You just saw him fighting for his life.
How can you say that?
Who do you think is the reason he's like that?
For whom did my Mu Jin give up everything and leave home?
I never told him to give everything up.
Didn't you love my Mu Jin?
I did.
I loved him, but...
I mean, it would be one thing if I hadn't known,
But I knew exactly what family he came from.
A penniless day labourer like Kim Mu Jin.
What's so appealing about that to me now?
- Do you think you can say anything? - If things stay as they are,
I'd have to take on all of Kim Mu Jin's burdens...
Without any help from you.
Honestly, I'm not confident I can do that.
We only dated for one year.
And we're not married.
I'm having a hard enough time as it is.
How am I supposed to know...
How bad his disability from the crash will be?
Why would I just take on all of that?
I can't do it. I don't want to.
Are you...
Even human?
Are you?
Because of a pathetic girl like you, my Mu Jin...
I don't want to waste another word on a snob like you,
So don't ever contact us again.
What is this?
It's a voice recorder.
When Mu Jin wakes up,
Please play this for him.
Mu Jin...
Is not the kind of person who gives up on me easily.
This is what it would take for him to finally give up on me.
So you planned this from the start...
I'm sorry to have caused you this unnecessary worry.
The 100,000 dollars...
Do you still need the money?
I don't need it.
Are you okay?
The doctor said everything's normal except for the fracture.
You don't have to worry too much.
Give me my phone.
It's not here.
Do you think you lost it?
What happened?
How long has it been since I got hurt?
Three days.
Gyu Rim...
Gyu Rim must be so worried.
Gyu Rim already came by.
Did you tell her everything?
Did you tell her I was hurt at a construction site?
No, I just said you were walking,
And got struck by lightning out of the blue.
No...
I just told her I wasn't sure what happened.
And that I rushed over as soon as I got the call.
If you tell her the truth, you're dead.
Well, I'm dead either way.
- What? - It's nothing.
Gyu Rim is really worried, right?
Well...
She came the first day but hasn't been back since.
She hasn't even called to ask how you're doing.
What are you doing? Are you trying to go see her...
In your condition?
- Call Gyu Rim for me. - Oh, honestly.
The number you dialled is not available.
- Please leave a message... - She's not answering.
She must be busy.
Try again.
- The number you have dialled... - Not picking up.
Text Gyu Rim and tell her I'm awake...
And not to worry.
Okay.
Jung Woo, could you give us a minute?
- Okay. - Thanks.
Are you okay?
I'm okay.
Sorry for scaring you.
I have something to tell you.
I thought about waiting until you're fully recovered,
But I think it's better to tell you sooner.
What is it?
It's about Han Gyu Rim,
The woman you gave up everything for.
Did you see Gyu Rim?
Gyu Rim called me and asked to meet.
Just give me 100,000 dollars.
100,000 dollars?
100,000 dollars for leaving Mu Jin.
That sounds like a pretty good deal, don't you think?
(Seized Item)
To be honest,
When I heard Mu Jin was from a rich family,
I was surprised, but a part of me was thrilled.
I thought, "Am I going to be a Cinderella,"
"just like in the movies?"
"I won't have to struggle through this miserable life anymore."
I was so happy. Truly.
If things stay as they are,
I'd have to take on all of Kim Mu Jin's burdens...
Without any help from you.
Honestly, I'm not confident I can do that.
We only dated for one year.
And we're not married.
I'm having a hard enough time as it is.
How am I supposed to know...
How bad his disability from the crash will be?
Why would I just take on all of that?
I can't do it. I don't want to.
Stop it.
What did you do to Gyu Rim?
What could I possibly have done to make Han Gyu Rim say all that?
I want to be alone.
Okay. Get some rest.
Yes.
Thank you for showing us.
- Thank you. - Goodbye.
One more time.
- Are you okay? - Yes. Thanks.
Thanks.
Who is it?
Is Gyu Rim here?
Who?
Han Gyu Rim.
Didn't you just come out of this house?
What? What's so strange about me coming out of my own house?
Oh, you must have moved in.
Then the people who lived here before...
How should I know?
Even after they got an eviction notice,
They were such a pain and refused to leave.
(Gyu Rim)
The number you have dialled is not in service.
Please check the number and try again.
(8 years later)
(Most Precious Thing In The World)
It's a pouch, right?
What's this? A puppy?
- Is this Yun Hu's puppy? - Yes.
- It's so cute. - Isn't it pretty?
It's pretty.
- Is this Jin Ju's teddy bear? - Yes.
This must be the teddy bear you cherish the most.
Five hearts.
This is drawn so well.
Who is this?
Who is this person that our Gyeol thinks...
Is the most precious in the world?
It's my mom.
Your mom must be so happy.
But Gyeol, what's this dot?
That's my dad.
- That's your dad? - Yes.
But he's still a precious dad, right?
Seeing as you drew him in, even if it's just a dot.
Well, he is the reason I was born.
I think I'm grateful for just about that much.
Oh, right.
Mom.
- Son, you're home? - Mom.
So, how was school?
- Was it fun? - Yes, it was fun.
Mom, here.
What's this?
Gyeol, who is this pretty lady?
It's you, Mom.
My teacher told us to draw the most precious thing in the world.
Am I the most precious person in the world to you?
Yes.
I'm representing my class in the drawing contest next week.
Really? Gyeol, you're the best.
You must be so happy, ma'am.
You have a kind and pretty daughter-in-law,
And a smart and cute grandson.
Of course I am.
It's absolutely wonderful.
Why do you call me your grandson?
And why is my mom your daughter-in-law?
Why are you lying?
I see your mom and you...
As my own daughter-in-law and grandson. That's what I meant.
Goodness, how can such a little thing be so prickly?
- Take care. - Enjoy your food and come again.
- Goodbye. - Hey.
Hey, don't be like that, okay?
We've known each other for ages, so why don't we really...
Make your mom my daughter-in-law and you my grandson?
No way.
Han Gyeol.
Are you going to keep being rude to her?
But if she keeps lying, what if you can't get married?
Goodness...
Why wouldn't she be able to get married?
My Heung Sik is right there waiting for her.
Exactly. That's the problem.
What? What in the world are you talking about?
What's the problem with my son waiting for her?
Okay, that's enough. Let's get back to work.
You don't know what you're talking about, do you?
In this whole wide world,
There's no one like my son, you hear?
I don't care. My mom's too good for him.
Even if it were Kim Woo Bin, my mom would still be too good for him.
What am I going to do with you?
You know nothing, but you have such high standards.
Gyeol, can you check my phone?
(Gyu Young)
It's Gyu Young.
Can you answer it for me?
Hey, you know that white dress I bought last month?
The flowy, chiffon one. I need to wear it tomorrow,
- take it to the dry cleaners now. - Is mom your secretary, Auntie?
You should do your own errands, Auntie.
Stop bossing my busy mom around.
Hey.
Gyeol.
That's right. Good job, Gyeol.
All that pent-up frustration I had,
Just melted away.
Your aunt, that little pest,
Needs to be put in her place just like that.
You did great. Smart boy.
Darn it. That little brat.
Hi, honey.
No, I was planning to wear it to your cousin's wedding tomorrow,
And I was going to ask my sister to get it dry-cleaned.
But Han Gyeol, that little pipsqueak,
Told me not to order his mom around...
Really? No, I was just upset, that's all.
Are you really going to buy me a new outfit?
You're the best.
Yes. Come in.
It's time for Ms. Song Ji Young's appointment.
Send her in, please.
Okay.
Honey, okay, I'll see you after work.
(Dr. Han Gyu Young)
What can I do for you today?
Well, can I...
Can I become Suzy?
Excuse me?
- Suzy? - Yes.
That would be difficult, wouldn't it?
Extremely difficult.
Even if you were to die and be reborn,
I don't think it would be possible.
(Hospital Revenue: Incentives)
Of course, it won't be easy, but nothing is impossible, right?
Shall we find a solution together, step by step?
Okay.
Excuse me. Time to get up.
It's after 3pm.
If you were sleeping when I left for school,
By the time I get home, shouldn't you at least be awake?
How long are you planning to live like this?
You're young with your whole life ahead of you.
Don't you want to start living your life properly?
You talk like an old man.
You're just a kid. Why do you talk like that?
Don't change the subject.
Are you going to get your act together or not?
Whether I get my act together or not,
What's it to you?
If you don't get your act together, it's hard on my mom.
Well, look at the dutiful son.
It's enough to make people without sons jealous.
Hey, Han Gyeol.
As I always tell you,
My life is mine, and your life is yours.
From now on, let's stay out of each other's lives.
- Deal? - We're family, not strangers.
How can you say that?
Oh my goodness. Look at that cool expression.
I can't handle it.
I think I'm dying.
If what I'm looking at isn't an angel, what is it?
When Gyu Seo graduates next year, I might just drop out.
There's no point in coming to school if Gyu Seo isn't here.
- He's so handsome. - He's gorgeous.
Can I have one of these?
- Hey, I'll take one too. - Go ahead.
Idol trainees are on another level.
I know.
This is giving me a serious inferiority complex.
Are you sure it's relative?
- And not absolute? - Time for soccer.
We've got to play soccer during lunch.
Hey, you know what?
I heard his twin sister goes to our school too.
If she's his twin, don't you think she'd be gorgeous?
Oh, come on. You idiot.
Hey, last year you kept saying you couldn't stand her,
And you threw a fit to switch partners. Did you forget?
Why would you bring her up now?
You want to play? Want to join us?
He and her... They're twins?
We all have to stay strong.
I've still got some food left.
- Gyu Min. Han Gyu Min. - Wake up.
Hey, please just set me up with Gyu Seo once.
Oh, please.
Hey, Gyu Min, you like tteokbokki, don't you?
I know a killer place and it'll be my treat,
So how about we go with Gyu Seo?
Can't you just invite us over to your house once?
When's your birthday?
Oh, wait. Since you're twins with Gyu Seo,
It's September 10, right?
Look. I'm not close with Han Gyu Seo.
If you want to see him, go ask him yourselves,
And meet up with him.
And take all of this back.
- Hey, come on. - Gyu Min.
Stop it. I'm going home.
Hey, Han Gyu Min. Let's go home.
Hey, where are you going?
- Hey, Han Gyu Seo. - Hey, Su Min.
- Thanks. I'm going home. - Bye.
Hey, Han Gyu Min. Hey, wait up.
Stay away from me, Han Gyu Seo.
I'm begging you, please stop acting like we're close.
Hey, how can I be acting?
We just are close.
Hey.
Hey, we're family, and we're twins.
Wouldn't it be weirder to pretend we're not close?
Do you have any idea how much trouble you cause me?
Because of you, I have no life of my own. None.
I just...
Want to fly under the radar and live quietly.
Please, let's just pretend we're strangers,
At least at school.
All right, fine. I'm sorry.
But, well...
You're not sulking, are you?
You scared me.
Hey, you startled me.
We're outside the school gates, so this doesn't count as school.
I'll do what you said inside the school,
So outside of school, I can do what I want, right?
Time to act close.
You know you're a real pain, right?
I guess I can be.
- Why are you taking my bag? - Carrying things stunts growth.
My dear Gyu Min,
You should grow every last centimetre you can.
Hey, get back here. Give me my bag.
Hey, give it back.
My dear Gyu Min, grow up big and strong...
And be in a beauty pageant.
Hey. Then give me some of yours.
Are you still mad?
Want to get some tteokbokki?
- It's my treat. - You go eat a lot.
Do you know how bad tteokbokki is for losing weight?
I thought you weren't on a diet.
I mean, you were devouring jajangmyeon yesterday,
So I thought you'd given up on your diet.
I am on a diet.
I'm just not losing any weight.
You're the one who suggested jajangmyeon.
Han Gyu Seo. Hey.
Who are you?
Why have you been following us around for days?
Are you...
The woman who abandoned us?
The one who fell for another man...
And ran off with all our money? Are you that gold digger?
Tell me, ma'am.
Oh, I'm sorry for following you.
My daughter has a huge crush on you,
And she's become lovesick.
I wondered how handsome you must be...
To make her sick, so I came to see for myself.
So why are you so needlessly handsome, like a pop idol,
Making me come back to see you?
You should just make your debut.
So I can watch you on TV at home.
My arm hurts.
Let's go.
(No couples allowed.)
(Dasolo welcomes solo diners, friends, and families.)
All right, one T-bone for table three,
- and one tomato pasta. - Yes, Chef.
One T-bone.
When was this made?
An hour ago.
Okay, it's fine.
- Just more salt and pepper. - Yes, Chef.
You'll break it apart like that. Fold it inward like this.
Yes, Chef.
Everyone, this place absolutely lives up to the hype.
First of all, the taste is beyond words.
The quality of every single ingredient is...
Wow, can you see this?
It's absolutely amazing. First, the vegetables.
They're so incredibly crisp and fresh,
It's like they were just picked.
The meat's flavour, juiciness, and cook...
Nothing is lacking.
But...
This place isn't just famous for its food, is it?
Right.
Is this really a couples' inferno and singles' paradise?
Unmarried couples who don't show up...
On a certificate of family relations,
Male friends, female friends, man, man-man, woman-woman, anyway...
Are all couples really banned from entering and dining?
That's what I need to confirm now.
At a glance,
It looks normal.
Is everyone family? Or are they married?
Excuse me.
Are you really married?
Wait, aren't you high school students?
We aren't students. We just look young for our age.
Please show me your certificate.
Oh, we forgot to bring it.
You can access it on your phone these days.
If you go to the Government24 website...
What kind of restaurant asks customers...
For their certificate of family relations?
Are you even allowed to demand our personal information like this?
That has always been the rule here.
If you don't like it, you can go to another restaurant.
I won't charge you for your meal, so please leave now.
Honey, let's go.
Fine, we'll leave.
Could you please clear this table?
Chef, we need to talk.
Go ahead.
Hey, you crazy...
You're a psycho.
Of all people, you had to pick a fight with a customer,
And for such a ridiculous reason?
Ridiculous reason?
When we opened this place, you said it would be fun.
What on earth is the problem?
You not knowing what the problem is, is the problem.
Why, because of your ridiculous, stubborn rule,
Do perfectly fine couples have to sit at separate tables,
Eating their meals wistfully like star-crossed lovers,
And then reunite outside like they're long-lost family?
Who do you think you are, tearing couples apart like this?
What are you, the local relationship-wrecker?
If they don't like it, they can eat somewhere else.
Are you running a charity?
Are you trying to keep all the other places in business?
Because of you, since we opened,
Do you know...
We bombed on Valentine's Day, White Day, and Christmas?
On the days that are peak season for everyone else,
Why are you so determined to ruin things for me?
This is all because of Han Gyu Rim...
Are you two fighting again?
Your combined age is nearly 70 now. Aren't you embarrassed?
Seo Hyun, you're just in time.
Listen to this and you be the judge.
For a restaurant like this,
To have a policy of not accepting couples...
Does that make any sense?
Well, I'm sure some customers get upset.
But a lot of customers come here...
Specifically because it's fun, right?
Single people say this place is like a paradise for them.
You even get their full support, don't you?
Right, Jang Seo Hyun.
You'd side with Kim Mu Jin even if he betrayed the country.
I was an idiot to ask you.
I'm heading out.
We're not done talking. Where are you going?
Honestly,
I don't know why we have to argue about this to this extent.
But if you're this stressed about it,
I'll think about it again.
Let's talk again tomorrow before we open.
If we keep going like this, we'll just get emotional.
Don't you get tired of it?
Of what?
Just staring at his back because he's not interested in you.
Like this.
I've seen it so much that I'm used to it now.
You're not getting any younger.
- How long are you going to... - I'll only do it until I'm 40.
Do what until you're 40?
I've liked him since I was ten years old.
So 40 makes it 30 years, right?
If he still doesn't love me by then, I'm planning to stop.
You've found something else to tease me about, haven't you?
On the day you complete 30 years of your one-sided love,
Whether it works out or not,
I'll give you a gold medal.
30 Years of doing anything...
Deserves that much praise and respect.
If you're going to give me one, make it solid gold.
Make the ribbon and the medal solid gold.
A full 30 grams.
Are you serious?
Do you know how expensive gold is these days?
Seriously...
Jung Woo, I'm leaving. See you later.
She's out of her mind.
Mu Jin.
Where are you going?
Just out.
Let's eat together next time.
Where?
Are you going to meet a woman?
It's not like that.
Then let's go together. I'll just go with you.
Hey.
All right.
Got it.
So close.
- Enjoy it. - Thank you.
Hey, you got a hot dog?
Is one hot dog going to be enough for you?
Eat that, finish what you need to do, and head home first.
It's fine. I have an email to send anyway.
Don't mind me. Do what you were doing.
You sure?
Okay.
Time to play.
(Tyrant Of Steel)
Got him.
- Okay. - How can someone change so much?
Yes, I dodged it.
I wonder if he really hit his head back then.
That's it. I got it.
This is tough.
Darn it.
Are you cursing because you got fourth place?
- Darn it. - Why? What's wrong?
This jerk kept getting in my way and using items to send me flying.
What the heck?
Look, this bastard did the same thing last time.
Last time, when I'd almost defeated the boss,
He swooped in, landed the final blow, and stole it.
He took all the points and levelled up,
And what did I get?
Who plays a game with such terrible sportsmanship?
Some jobless punk who's just cooped up at home.
I'm so pissed.
Hey, you.
- What are you doing? - What?
I mean, you kept messing with me.
You did the same thing when I was fighting the boss.
I didn't realise. I'm sorry. It was a mistake.
(I didn't realise. I'm sorry. It was a mistake.)
What? "You didn't realise"? "It was a mistake"?
If you're making such mistakes without realising it,
You must be a noob. Then stick to your own level.
Let's not play like that, okay?
Excuse me, I said it was a mistake and even apologised,
But you're being way too harsh.
Oh my...
You don't think about what you've done,
But you think my words are too harsh?
After you maliciously and deliberately messed me up,
You think saying, "I didn't know, it was a mistake" makes it all okay?
I heard he turns into a complete child when he gets into a game,
And Jung Woo was right.
You can't just let guys like this get away with it.
(It's just a game. Why are you taking it seriously...)
Oh, come on. Why is he being like this?
What is his problem?
You want a piece of me?
Why is he saying strange things?
Gosh, seriously.
Mom.
Hey, who does this person think he is,
Talking to my precious son and threatening him like that?
Gyeol, move aside.
- Move. - Hey.
Move, move.
Oh, for goodness' sake.
Mom, a person like that is better off ignored.
No, you have to shut these jerks down from the get-go.
Why do you think they call them items?
They're there for you to use. Why is he picking a fight...
When he only lost because he's not good enough?
What? Is this guy asking for a fight in real life?
Don't tell him our address.
What if he comes and tries to hurt us?
Guys like this are just pathetic cowards.
Tell them to show up, and they won't even dare.
They just act tough online.
Still, what if he actually shows up?
Don't you worry. Mom is here for you.
I'll protect you no matter what, so don't you worry about a thing.
He sounds like a little kid. What does he think he's doing?
What school does he go to?
(What are you going to do if I don't back down?)
Oh, you little brat. You've really asked for it now.
Let's settle this today.
See? You shouldn't have come, right?
No. It was fun.
Where else could I see a show like this for free?
I saw a side of you today I never saw when you were 12.
You were so cute and relatable.
- Go on inside. - Wait a second.
Hi, Mom. I'm right outside. Is there any food?
Yes, okay. I'll be right in.
You came all this way. Stay and eat.
You like my mom's cooking, don't you?
What did he do to deserve a meal?
- Chairman, hello. - Dad.
What? Am I wrong?
He's always treating my daughter like dirt.
Why would I feed him a warm meal? Right?
Why are you being like this?
Hey, why are you sending such mixed signals?
Why did you give her a ride?
And why would you agree to eat food from my wife?
No, it's not like that, Dad.
Hold on. Let him speak for himself.
I'm sorry, Chairman,
But I've never given Seo Hyun mixed signals.
Oh, really?
You weren't confused?
He's right. I asked him to give me a ride.
And as a thank-you, I invited him to stay for dinner.
Dad, you don't even know what you're talking about.
This whole situation just makes me angrier.
It's not like you're lacking anything,
So why are you so hung up on a guy like this?
Hey. And what makes you so great?
Is my Seo Hyun not good enough for you?
No, sir. Absolutely not. That's not it at all.
- That's not it, right? - That's right.
You didn't give her mixed signals,
And Seo Hyun isn't lacking anything. This is your problem.
Dad.
You're so frustrating.
You need to send some mixed signals sometimes.
If she pushes, you let yourself get pushed a little,
And then you have to pull her in. You get it?
What are you, Fort Knox?
You're just so buttoned up and rigid.
Come on. This is so frustrating.
- There's no food. Get going. - Yes, sir.
- You, come inside. - Dad.
I'll be in touch.
Good night.
- Mu Jin. - Go.
Just get in the elevator. Hurry.
Honey.
Do you like it?
Yes.
Marry me, Gyu Young.
Married?
I'll...
I'll give you the stars and the moon.
I'll make you so happy.
Marry me. Please.
Will you marry me?
Yes.
It's beautiful.
I love you.
I love you too.
Looks so good on you.
It's so beautiful. Does it look good on me?
Must be nice.
I remember when I was like that.
Good and beautiful things...
Seem to disappear so quickly.
They haven't disappeared.
You still have all of those things.
Right here,
And right here.
Stop.
Why is it suddenly so hot in here?
Should we head up now?
I'd like to get some rest.
Let me just finish this drink.
Cheers.
Oh, no.
Honey, are you okay?
I'm going to the restroom.
- Wait here. - Okay.
When did you get this?
Does it look good on me?
Even if I'm being generous,
She looks like she could be 12 years older than you.
I don't know how you do it.
None of your business.
Looked like you were getting a ring.
You're not actually going to marry him, are you?
None of your business.
And what if I do?
Did the diamond blind you?
You think this is the first time I've gotten one of these?
Are you really going to marry him?
I'm seriously considering it.
His looks are decent enough, and his education isn't bad.
Most importantly, he's incredibly rich.
Does his character not matter to you?
He's rich enough that his character doesn't matter.
Happy now?
Have you saved any money?
I know a host who already bought an apartment.
Is that what you were trying to say?
Easy come, easy go.
Don't spend it as fast as you make it.
Buy a studio apartment or something.
You're the first person to find out about my job.
Is that what you wanted to say?
How am I supposed to react, then?
Should I ask, "Out of all the jobs in the world,"
"why did you become a gigolo?"
Should I be shocked and pass out?
Am I Han Gyu Rim?
Forget it.
I was an idiot for even asking.
That little brat.
Of all the jobs...
Whatever.
It's your life, not mine.
Mom.
Yes?
What was Dad like?
Why are you asking all of a sudden?
I was just wondering. My teacher asked about my dad today,
And I didn't know anything about him.
To be honest,
I never really cared before.
And I probably won't care in the future, either.
You don't have to tell me if you don't want to.
I'm not dying to know or anything.
He's your dad, so, of course, he was a good person.
And?
Was he handsome? Was he tall?
Did he look like me?
He was handsome and tall.
Let's see if you look like him.
You do look like him.
Is he still alive?
Yes.
Then,
Don't you miss him?
Do you miss him?
No.
All I need is you.
(Geumje Police Station)
I wasn't in my right mind due to stress.
I believe I was overly emotional.
I am sincerely reflecting on my actions.
Do you think that'll be enough?
Unbelievable.
What on earth did you say during a game...
That got you reported and brought in for questioning?
From what I've seen,
These things rarely become a formal investigation.
- Just how bad was it? - Hey, I'm a victim here too.
I was staring at the monitor and crying...
No, I was bleeding from my eyes from all the abuse I took.
Oh, well done. You trade insults,
And then you both come in for questioning.
You two are practically soulmates.
I wonder how old they are.
Who cares how old your soulmate is?
Just say you've got some mental problems...
And ask them to cut you a break.
Try to settle this amicably.
Darn it.
What? You want me to go with you as a lawyer?
No, it's fine.
I'll be back.
(Geumje Police Station)
Does he think he's Benjamin Button?
This is beyond regression.
How can he get more immature with age?
"I'll be back?" What's that supposed to mean?
I hope he doesn't come back.
Darn it.
(Police)
Let go of me.
Are you Kim Mu Jin?
Yes.
So, you must be Han Gyeol's...
Guardian?
The account does belong to Han Gyeol,
But I'm the one who wrote the comments.
You two should know better.
Please have a seat, both of you.
"You stupid son of a gun."
"Looking at what you're doing,"
"I feel so sorry for the mother who gave birth to you."
"She suffered for ten months..."
"just to give birth to a piece of garbage."
Han Gyu Rim.
Is this what you actually wrote?
Yes.
So, Kim Mu Jin.
"What the frickin' heck?"
"Instead of worrying about my mom, you should worry about yours."
"Is she even still alive?"
"Didn't she die of embarrassment already?"
This is what you wrote, right?
- Yes. - What was your intention?
State your cases one at a time.
I Didn't have some grand intention.
In the heat of the moment,
I got carried away.
Neither of you wants to press charges against each other, right?
That's right.
Since this is a first offence for both of you,
And you both seem remorseful, how about you settle this...
By writing and exchanging apologies?
If you get reported for trading insults again,
It won't end this easily next time.
- Understood. - Understood.
Let me see.
This isn't a good spot. Both of you, follow me.
Let me know when you're done writing your apologies.
Look...
Let's just hurry up and write apologies...
So we can get out of here.
(Geumje Police Station)
Are you going to run away again?
If you're running away, do it right.
So we never have to see each other again.
Mom.
My son.
Mom, you had a hard time, didn't you?
Gyeol kept insisting...
That he wanted to see you, so I brought him.
Is everything settled?
Here, eat this.
You shouldn't have.
(Love on the Menu)
Honey, let's go.
So that guy's her husband?
She already got married?
- Does he want to start over? - Hey.
So you do still like him.
- You're clearly not over him. - She has a son?
I think they said he's eight years old.
Han Gyu Rim and Mu Jin broke up eight years ago.
Chairman, if you would just...
I mean, if you would just pretend to be my father twice.
Let's go buy some clothes at the department store.
Clothes? Why all of a sudden?
You need them for the family meeting.
Who's having a family meeting?
- Gyu Young is. - What?